[Music]
hello everyone this is Frank defus and
welcome to holot talk the internet's
laser and holography talk show enjoyed
in over 42 countries throughout the
world and now here's this week's
[Music]
show Larry how are you it's Frank defus
hi Frank good to hear from you early
morning there for you huh yeah it is
just a little before 7:00 a.m. and just
having my morning coffee and
try to get woken up a little bit here
yeah I want to thank you first for uh
sending me the email it's always
interesting to see people doing the work
it takes a lot of work to get all that
information compiled and placed on the
web so it's good to see that people
actually access it and use it right I've
made good use of your website actually
usually with a show I have someone start
off by telling a little bit of their
history and holography I understand that
you've been involved for about 2 years
so relatively speaking uh for the time
frame of a itself you're a relative
newcomer but what got you started with
the
holography uh through some research that
I was doing I I'm a software uh engineer
uh by trade and I have an interest in uh
neural networks and uh and artificial
intelligence this kind of stuff okay and
uh I was looking for a way to implement
a neural network initially I was just
thinking with the
electronics uh and and uh did some
research and stumbled across a paper
that was talking about using uh
holography for uh doing interconnection
of Weights in a neural network okay and
uh the paper was relatively
understandable for me so uh I decided
Well maybe I could try something like
that and started looking around on the
uh internet and came across your website
uh and you were talking about doing a
laser pointer based holography okay and
I had just recently got it really cheap
laser pointer so I thought you know this
might almost be doable uh and then I uh
did more research uh try to try to find
uh a kit or something like that yeah and
came across the uh intergraph website uh
you may have even had a link to it there
and uh purchased one of their kits and
just started playing around with it and
uh something that I found with that kit
was that the first very first one I made
and in talking to other people they
often had the same experience that they
the first one you're you're able to make
it uh and actually get something usually
just because uh you don't really know
what you're doing at all and the
instructions in the kit are uh pretty
clear and if you just follow exactly
what they're saying uh then you
typically can get something uh then
being an engineer though then I thought
then you start playing around yes
exactly uh which was not so good in the
beginning the first kid I bought was uh
32 I think they're 2 and half by 2 and
1/2 inch plates and uh like I said the
first one came out and then the next 28
did not come out wow uh yeah I was
messing around with the the vibration
aspect of it and just different ways to
hold the plate and when I first started
doing it I had basically just a little
1ot by one foot piece of plywood and uh
glued the laser on a stick pretty much
following uh you know illustrations i'
seen around and uh and shot my first
hologram like that stuck the stick in a
little cup of sand that works so I
figured okay now I want to do more and I
need more space and everything you start
to grow from there uh and not realizing
all of the details you you do a little
trial and error there unfortunately in
my case there was a long trial and error
there but uh more error than success but
eventually then I uh you know I learned
to just modify one aspect at a time
exactly and uh the scientific process at
work yes and it's uh
it works if you do that uh you can
through process of elimination you can
find problems and uh and move ahead
start out with as few variables as
possible and then just add one at a time
yes yeah right what got you involved
with the multiplex that was quite a jump
yes that was and uh what did that was I
had been shooting some single beam
dentics and uh actually I tried pretty
much all of the experiments in uh Tong
jong's book that he provides uh in that
inter gra kit and uh was having fun with
that and still do have fun with that uh
just wanted to try different types of
things and realized I want to be able to
uh take output from my computer somehow
and uh and get that on a hologram so
again I turned to your website because I
had saw a couple of uh of holograms that
you did I think one was like a a grid
with a floating triangle oh okay yeah
and uh you had mentioned that you had
that output with a line of ronic and I
had earlier in my career I had been
doing book publishing and I knew what
align okay yeah the old 300s y exactly
so uh I figure okay again that's
something that's within the realm of me
actually doing because some of these
research papers are just so uh
theoretical that it's hard to put into
perspective what they're talking about
and get you know the real world uh what
that really means yeah uh so that's why
I enjoyed reading your articles because
you cross that line and you you showed
examples which is very important as I
was starting to get into this I found
that those descriptions just were
lacking for example just developing uh
one of the terms they use in there is uh
you put the plate in the bath and then
you agitate uh didn't really know what
agitate meant so uh anyway it helps to
to uh get in touch with somebody and
actually discuss what they're doing
somebody that has done it and that's
where the tography for has been uh uh
big uh source of information for me yes
people uh readily discuss uh what
they're doing and there's a whole bunch
of people on there doing many things all
the way from making their own film and
people just getting on board and uh lots
of information and lots of people
they're willing to talk about it yeah
once I got my mind around what the
multiplex Holograms were uh and not
having actually seen one in front of me
uh I thought it was easier than than
what it turned out to be each by
breaking down each piece into uh you
know of the of the entire task into
little pieces uh I could see uh that it
was doable M and started thinking about
a lot and and ended up oversimplifying
what was going on yeah and in fact when
I after I accomplished that task of
making My First multiplex hologram I
looked at my table and S and thought to
myself boy that looks awful simple
there's there's really not a whole lot
there but then after having gone through
month after month of of failures and
just moving things around and trying
different things out uh it it is easy to
just go crazy with it and over
complicate each
piece I just realized this weekend that
after being able to do this I almost
feel a little bit of a loss because I
enjoyed standing next to the table
previously I always used just a card
shutter and uh manually shutter for all
my exposures too the exposures are
within the realm of me being able to do
that when I got a more powerful laser
though my exposure time would drop and I
actually had to end up attenuating the
beam because I couldn't get like less
than a second accurate timing with that
uh but then moving to the multiplex
system and automating everything uh I I
found that my biggest Joy was actually
in implementing it all MH uh when it
comes down to it uh now I put a plate in
my plate holder and basically push a
button say go and leave the room and
come back and end up developing it and
I've kind of taken away from myself all
the joy that I had in in making it
itself yeah exactly yeah it's it's very
similar to I guess a cabinet maker or
any type of crafts person the part of
the website that I have up there for the
little holographic portraits takes into
consideration uh that people like to be
very Hands-On and it's it's very
Hands-On intensive takes a lot of time
to do one of those yes it does and uh
when I I I I initially read that uh
description that you had to try to do
that and was taking that path uh that
being using an LCD panel mhm uh and I
was having some issues because I had a
very weak laser I only had a 7M
unpolarized Heeney and as you know the
panel is polarized so uh initially I was
just trying to Pro Force it through the
panel and let whatever light was aligned
with the crystals come through and I was
just going to take what I got yeah but
unfortunately the exposures were just
way too long so yeah it didn't work out
for me so I moved to this uh DLP
projector I had found found a article
from uh some people at MIT about how to
utilize an off-the-shelf uh DLP
projector M uh as the image source and
that turned out to be a lot better for
me because that's based on mirrors yeah
and uh it was a self-contained projector
uh you know like the kind you would have
in an office or something like that mhm
and my table's really small it's uh 2T
by 3 ft uh by about 2 in thick M and uh
so it's kind of tough to get all the
pieces that I need and in fact I still
I'm not able to do a very large image I
can get about a 2 and 1 half by 2 and a
half image yeah uh inch image but uh and
obviously they're more dramatic the
bigger they are but this gives me a good
Proving Ground BEC uh as I was saying
before I've kind of not so involved
right now on on modifying my table and
getting things happening there because I
can get images off of it now I'm having
to look more at the creative of it and
the image the images themselves and um
having something uh worth looking at the
first couple of things I did actually
turned out to be almost what I would
have done with solid objects like a uh
key things but you know like a skull and
different things like this but having
access to uh rendering software that can
render these images uh for me and
utilizing uh effects kind of like uh
transparency and taking into count the
refractive index of glass if you were
rendering images like that uh I
anticipate being able to just do all
kinds of things that basically whatever
my mind can imagine yeah you render
objects that don't actually exist
exactly and things that would be nearly
impossible you could have tubes of light
bending out across the image plane and
stuff like that that would be rather
tough to do if you were doing it with
objects although there are some uh
artists from the 80s that have done
spectacular work uh that amazes me that
they're able to do that basically with
mirrors in glass still yeah but uh I
don't do that I can utilize the computer
to do that and uh it's uh very flexible
so it sounds to me like you're
approaching this more from an
engineering standpoint than it is a
creative well I guess maybe a marriage
of both really yes and and actually that
is what it is I I I feel uh motivated on
both sides U and as I mentioned before I
feel a little cheated now that I have
the thing built uh mechanically uh
enough to where I can generate the
Holograms and and having to spend more
time on the on the images themselves but
uh excuse me that doesn't mean that I
won't uh tear down the table and and go
back to shooting some single Bean
dynastics again oh yeah yeah do you have
any interest in doing uh people Yes
actually and that originally was what I
was interested in in looking at your
website and looking at the portraits in
fact early on I wasn't aware of of using
uh the multiplex technique for doing
people or other other objects that you
can capture on film and had purchased a
uh one of these military Rangefinder uh
Ruby pulse lasers and uh was going
through the process of trying to get
there with that however I found a couple
of of stumbling blocks along the way the
Ruby uh it's hard to find film that I
think it's 694 now wavelength and film
is not so sensitive there uh I think
some of the color film out there might
be sensitive uh to that wavelength uh
but then also this thing only has a one
pulse per second rep rate and so you
don't really see there's no beam to see
mhm and so I started becoming concerned
about the safety aspect of it and uh you
know how do I align this
thing I would have to do a split beam to
do people all of those it just looked
like too big of a task uh so at this
stage of the game anyway yeah I know
there are people out there doing it uh
professionals I don't know how many
people are not I came across somebody at
a university I think in Washington
that's doing interferometry with a uh a
ruby pulse laser and he's using uh PFG
from slav and he's able to do his work
with that but he has a lot of power that
he's ding on the plate yeah and he's
he's not expecting display holography
results from those experiments either
that's right yeah so have you thought
about doing film at all or would you
rather just keep everything electronic I
have thought about doing film and in
fact probably will and the reason is
that the uh contrast from this DLP
projector
uh it doesn't seem so great that the
difference between black and white the
black is not so black I see uh but it's
discernable and I'm sure that if I did
some uh some tweaking to the image
before I projected it to enhance the
contrast yes exactly that that would go
a long way uh I I don't have a lot of
experience though shooting like you
project the image from the projector
onto a a diffused screen of some sort uh
ground glass or something yes and I
don't have a lot of experience doing
that so when I look at the glass to me
it looks like it's just glowing
ridiculous uh you know uh after making
the hologram I see that it doesn't
affect it that much I get more of the
image than this glow that I see around
there uh and I'm sure that that is true
whether or not you're using film or a
DLP projector but I know with film you
can get extremely Crisp Images again
when I was first starting out I was
looking at your website and you had one
particular a little uh apparatus there I
sorry I'm going from memory but several
several month I'll have to go from
memory too because I haven't been on
there in a while either you had some
kind of a cage thing uh I think that's
the term you used a cage basically uh it
was a uh a frame of some sort that you
slid in a plate and a piece of uh film
holder and a piece of diffused glass uh
actually I think that was set up to do
holographic logos corporate logos and
things of that nature exactly so I made
a mini version of that out of a picture
frame that was about 5 by seven in and
it had multiple slots in it so you could
put multiple panes it was made for uh
simulating like a 3d effect with photos
and so I used one of those slots for the
diffused glass and one for holding the
Hologram and one for holding a a film
holder with a piece of film that I had
placed in there yeah and then you had
two mirrors off to the sides one at
Brewster's angle and one directing light
directly in and I did this on that
little one foot by one foot board that I
had just glued everything down onto that
board yeah uh and then with a diode I
was using the diode that came with the
intergraph kit and just took the lens
off and expanded the beam so that the
single beam uh in your setup was
creating object beam and reference beam
yeah and uh that was the first time uh
and and then got the beautiful hologram
from that film great extremely crisp
there were there were many fine lines on
this particular piece of film and
everything came out fantastic I'm happy
to hear that I I really am happy to hear
that great yeah you're you do have value
there Frank yeah that's good because you
never know what's going on I mean unless
someone sends you an email I mean
there's so many people that visit the
website but unless someone sends you an
email you never know what's going on
with anyone right that's true and in
fact even with this uh Multiplex stuff
when I first posted the uh my first
results on The Forum uh I thought boy uh
probably nobody's working on this and
now I've gone back and looked at the
Forum and there's at least four or five
other people who have uh uh gone about
as far as I have on there yeah every so
often I'll pick an email up that uh you
know someone has visited there and they
they've started to uh but there there's
a there's a number of different
documents you know I mean this goes back
a long time this uh Multiplex holography
yeah so there's a number of different
documents out there uh basically I I
mean some of them actually require
specialized equipment that it's well
beyond either the realm of building it
yourself or obtaining it financially so
what I tried to do was come up with a a
very simple way of of doing it on a on a
tabletop the whole part of the uh way
that I have the table geometry set up is
so that the slits aren't parallel with
the person looking at the Hologram
basically what the slits wind up doing
is when you're walking past the Hologram
and you look at the Hologram the slits
are actually about 9 or 10 in out in
front of the plate but not only that
you're not looking directly through them
they're at a 45° angle right so the the
bottom part of the slits would be about
9 or 10 Ines out from the plate and then
the slits themselves travel to 45° angle
and continue to go further out and the
further out you get the more any type of
irregularity that would be in the
Hologram would become blurred and you
wouldn't notice it right now on my table
I have uh such a limited space I can
only the the diffuse screen is only
actually 5 in away from the SL yeah
that's not too bad either though no that
is a doable thing and I now I have I
have not uh shot an H1 yet on this table
that is bright enough to make an H2 uh
so I can view it in white light yeah I
saw your email on that you said one time
you did a single shot that was bright
right and then you did a multiplex that
was not bright now let me ask you this
were you using the uh were you using the
DLP for for both of those shots yes I
was and in fact that was an error uh in
my stepper motor uh circuit uh I just
stumbled across this happen to have my
hand setting on the table while I was
telling the system to go through a run
through so I could watch what was going
on and try to figure out what was going
on and in fact every time my shutter
open my shutter is based on it's
homemade and it's based on a rotary
solenoid okay uh and uh with like a
little uh airplane uh propeller type
thing for the shutter itself and uh
every time it would activate
uh uh there was like a large current
Spike or a voltage Spike that got onto
my board uh that is driving the stepper
motor which told it to take a step one
tiny little step right when the shutter
opened unfortunately so that is what
I've traced it to being and it happened
for every slit I see uh and that'll do
it yeah that will do it and uh I'm sure
I have some other issues with uh
vibration on my table because the other
since I fixed that problem uh I've shot
a couple of more Holograms since then
and each slit is not exactly or even
necessarily close to the same density in
exposure uh mostly noticeable after it's
been bleached I can see uh the light
coming through it that there's some that
are better looking than others huh
uh uh what else did I want to talk yeah
I've I've noticed that many times to
some degree not an extreme degree by
doing them by hand uhhuh but I'm curious
as to what would be the uh the culprit
there if I'm still thinking uh that
there's a possibility that my slit the
slit itself is moving a little bit now
when when you put the slit uh up to the
plate is it in uh physically contacting
the plate yes I have the slits on fairly
thin uh construction board uhhuh okay I
put that by hand into the plate holder
is one unit the plate holder uh contains
the slit and the like yeah I see uh so I
have my slit It's mounted uh it's
controlled with a stepper motor how far
away from your plate is the slit uh I
tried to get it either right on top or
within a millimeter or so okay that's
that's pretty darn close yeah I've tried
uh I've tried to keep it both on and off
if you keep it too far away from the
plate then it starts to cast The Shadow
mhm your slits should actually be
running horizontal to the uh to the
surface of the table right yes yes so if
you're coming in at an angle I'm
assuming you're not using an overhead
reference beam correct that's right so
if you're coming in at an angle the only
shadow that you would cast would be the
top part of the slit the longer parallel
uh edges of the slit would not cast
Shadows right now uh one thing I've
learned recently is that you can uh now
in my case I'm moving the slit so the
plate is in the plate holder fixed the
slit moves from top to bottom if you're
looking at my table uh only because
there's some uh I forget the term they
use but it's kind of sloppy the
mechanical movement with the motor and
this and this little slide that I'm
using to move the stage is a little
sloppy so I'm utilizing gravity there
absolutely tugging down on the thing yes
don't go against gravity use it to your
advantage right basically what you're
saying is when you finish with this you
find out that you have higher density in
some exposures compared to others yes
and I've seen that on all of them even
after I uh fixed this problem with the
motor moving right when the shutter
opened would you say that every third
slit it's doing it on every hologram you
do you notice any patterns there's any
patterns at all whatsoever there isn't
uh uh actually the first one I shot
there was a basically a dead slit in the
same place each time and it turned out
that the the uh program that I wrote to
display the images had a bug in it and
this particular image that I was loading
it didn't scale right it just displayed
black so that one I was able to tell
because I shot two Holograms in a row
and the same slit on both of them was
was empty okay
uh what I tend to do I consider myself a
good troubleshooter so I basically look
at the entire
uh uh job and basically throw everything
at it uh knowing that I had to move the
slit that I had to have the projector I
had to split the beam Etc uh put
everything on the table and uh and just
go for it and then look at the results
yeah uh and try to work backwards from
then again learning early on that you
have to just modify one thing at a time
uh and I usually pretty quickly can find
out what the thing you know whatever the
issue is uh I haven't shot enough I only
shoot about maybe two or three a week
wow wow that's a lot and uh two or three
Holograms a week I think it would be
with something well of course your's an
automated how long does it take for the
automation to go through its entire
process uh it depends on how much settle
time usually uh lately because I've been
seeing these uh variations in density
I've been having like 3 minutes of
settle time so I expose for about 15
seconds and then settle for uh 3 minutes
and then I'm shooting between 25 and 30
exposur exposures so uh it could take a
couple hours
and uh I was just thinking the other
night in fact I may add a feature to my
software that I can just program in a
specific actual time and just tell it
like a 2:00 in the morning start running
MH uh up until now I put the plate in
until Tell It Go and then I leave the
room when does your stepper motor kick
in right as the other exposure is
completed or right before the exposure
begins at the end of the exposure so at
the end of so it's already in place and
and is settling has settled for that uh
period of time yeah yeah that's good and
uh although I may not uh you know
there's delays you have to put in in
cating it in the software you have to
you have to emulate in a way how you do
it manually that's the approach that
I've been taking and uh so I may not
have a long enough Delay from the time I
close the shutter till the time I start
moving I know it just the light just has
to be
gone and uh no light H in the plate then
it's safe to move uh but I haven't I
could put you know even a second or two
it doesn't really really matter if you
have uh that kind of timing going on in
it well that's incredible little machine
that you've put together thank you that
would cost several $100,000 I think if
uh to purchase something has been amazed
uh amazing to me is that I looked around
I've seen systems that go from like
20,000 to 200,000 yeah and uh I am less
than $1,000 on this table and I bought
uh the more expensive pieces I have
purchased through eBay like uh I have
the table itself is a Newport
workstation uh so it's very sturdy it's
made for doing stuff like this ESS
except it's not very thick I still end
up floating this on in tube and okay uh
for vibration isolation but it's great
it's like rock solid as far as the
surface goes AB it's got a steel surface
on it so I can use magnets I found these
round uh magnets that you might put on a
cupboard or something and and to hold
keys or something like that they they
have about a 25 lb holding force and so
uh
all of my optic stands are based on
basically uh these magnets I did get
some uh post holders so I can keep
everything at approximately the same
height mhm uh and then I did spend some
money on a spatial filter and on my
laser I have a 20 M Heeney right now mhm
uh but everything pretty much I just
tried to to make by hand and and bought
the components off of eBay the stepper
motor came with a lead screw on it uh
and that was about $35 off of eBay the
projector itself I only paid $50 for no
kidding and that right when I got it
they were used ones without a bulb were
going for about $50 on eBay now they're
going for about1 150 because people
realize they can use them for home uh
theaters oh and they are wonderful for
that in fact I felt a little bad about
tearing this one apart because I was uh
shining a laser or not a laser a light
just a white light source through it had
a beautiful image on the on the wall
there but uh this one has an internal
frame Grabber in it so you can hook up
uh even a vcr and uh grab frames from it
and it'll it'll hold them perfectly
still and there's no uh no artifacts
from the tape that you can see MH uh or
you can plug a a s video camera or VGA
and I'm just using the uh VGA side of it
yeah you could possibly work things out
where you could do live images if you
can use a camera yeah grab grab those
images of someone sitting in a chair and
have the Hologram made as the camera
moves yes yeah uh uh that's one thing
that's great about it being uh connected
to the computer and essentially in real
time you're you're projecting the image
whatever's coming into the projector
gets projected in real time yeah I
noticed you started out with a lot of
exposures and then in your email you had
said you're going to try four or eight
right I wanted to go uh early on before
I knew that the stepper motor was moving
during the exposure I wanted to see if
there was some issue with having a small
slit the first ones that I shot the slit
was about 2 to 3 millim mhm and how many
exposures were you doing I was doing uh
between 27 and 30 uhhuh uh I'm shooting
on a 4x5 plate okay and uh my my uh
plate holder basically only holds the
plate on one Edge uh there's two screws
that push it up against a metal bar and
it's plenty stable uh that that is on a
post uh regular Optics post holder uh
and then with a magnet onto the table
and uh uh I was thinking that maybe uh
you know the slit was too thin and I was
casting mostly Shadow across there or
something like that so that's why I was
I decided to go to to uh fewer frames
fewer yeah and uh in fact uh I had shot
one with uh it ended up being seven
frames because I didn't calculate and
take into effect that the the uh plate
holder has is masking some of the plate
there while it's was holding it m so I
ended up with seven uh but uh there
still is there I want to see what they
look like in white light though uh yeah
in the room that I shoot this in it's a
really small little washroom and so uh
when I project the real image or I'm
looking at the virtual image of one of
the multiplexes I just shot I have to
kind of crane my neck and stick my head
in between a small space and then on top
of that I'm looking at it laser
illuminated and my eyes not so sensitive
at that uh wavelength I'd much rather uh
look at it green or something if if
they're done properly they are very
impressive as laser transmission
Holograms yes the ones that uh when I
when I look into it uh The Parallax that
I see there is incredible the fact that
you don't have to cross your eyes and I
mean when there's more than eight uh
like the first ones that I shot were 27
uh uh frames there uh you can go from
side to side and you would swear that
there's a 3D object there absolutely it
it it that just I I'm really happy that
I I went through the entire process and
and actually got to see the thing uh
right in front of my eyes to realize how
good it actually is uh there's lots of
drawings and and things in these papers
that are out there on the web but to
actually see it uh is amazing now I have
when do you see it I don't know if you
you'll ever do one of these or not but
wait until you see somebody that you
know right that's what I was and I'll
tell you what the hair will stand up on
your arms and your neck when you seen
people get that reaction when I show
them this little face that I've done uh
and then I tell them just imagine if
that was your face in there and they
give me the strangest look they they get
what I'm saying there uh that it's a
very strange uh sensation and I agree
with some uh statements you made on your
website there about about a motive for
people that may want to have uh have
these things yeah is is seeing somebody
that you know or uh you know that's my
boat that's my house things that you
know and recognize seeing them in and a
three dimension like that right there in
your hand is just uh powerful basically
it's the technique that you really have
to get down and uh everything else
pretty much falls into place you sent me
a link to a web page that was on the
holography form and I went there and I
took a look and saw a few of your photos
and it this is great this this guy is
really doing this with with his own
homemade equipment yes and uh my poor
daughter when I started she was 14 now
she's 16 and all she's heard from me is
is interference and defraction all these
crazy terms and and look quick come over
here and look at this look at
this she's had to put it put up with it
for a while but uh and in fact she's
made a couple herself but I don't know
she just doesn't H have a a spark in her
that says oh I want to do that it's it's
it's uh very satisfying to me and it's
just a bunch of gobble a to her right
now yeah yeah well you know that's that
age is she looking forward to a career
in science and technology I don't know
she is Artistic okay uh and in fact she
likes working with Photoshop so I told
her you know we can work uh together and
you can do some uh some artistic things
in Photoshop and I can incorporate them
into the holography that I'm doing so uh
that's a way to get her uh into it even
though she's not uh interested in the
technical aspect uh definitely the
artistic aspect uh is there technology
and uh creativity artistic talents all
rolled into one what are your plans for
the future now with all this I'm going
to continue to uh
work with the table and try to get
things uh more solid one of the
directions I want to go is to try a full
Parallax
hologram uh which would essentially be
an array instead of having vertical
slits you have an array of rectangles in
essence that's interesting uh so that's
one thing that I was thinking about
trying uh I also uh still have an
interest in the other scientific uh
neural network stuff uh but again that's
going to be something way down the road
but I at least I'll have a platform to
learn more about light uh and what the
limits are like I said you read some of
these papers and they're just hugely
complex and then you realize all you
need is a piece of glass and a laser to
do something yeah so uh now I know you
know I need to still find out what the
limits are and what I can afford uh in
my budget what I can't afford uh and
just kind of keep moving towards uh
understanding the whole thing is I treat
it just as a learning experience
and uh just keep learning
yeah all right Larry is there anything
you want to add that we didn't cover uh
no I don't think so um I'm pretty much
covered I appreciate you having me on
you'll keep you'll keep in touch and let
me know how your experiments continue to
go too absolutely and I'll be posting
more uh on the Forum as I uh get a
little bit better I want to have cleaner
looking images and uh I do want to
mention if you don't mind me dropping a
couple names some people have helped me
and I just mentioned Desh uh also Al
yourself many of your documents on that
website have been a great value I print
them out and then I've read them over
and over again so I want to thank you
for that also uh Steve McGrew has been a
big help to me okay uh he's been willing
to uh give me little hints and just talk
it over and also Jason sapan in uh New
York does that as a living he actually
is using film and uh he had some
valuable insights as well so I try to
make use of uh of the talent that's out
there and there are some people who
willing to talk to you and some who
would rather not and I understand that
because that's their business and uh you
know you don't want to compete or have
be seen as a competitor unless you are a
competitor and then you know you have to
be uh honest about what you're doing
yeah so uh yeah great wish everybody
good luck on what they're doing and uh
just keep up making the Holograms all
right all right FK Larry Dario you have
a good rest of the week all right thank
you all right thanks for being on the
show talk to you later
bye
e
for